嘿  小玛
Hey, mads.
今天天气真不错啊
What a beautiful day.
我看见了心形的云朵
I see heart shapes in the clouds,
和闻起来像茉莉和热狗的空气
and the air smells like Jasmine and hot dogs.
我得到了一张匿名情书
I got a note from a secret admirer.
你真得到了
You did?
哇  刚才那真不是我们的风格
Wow, that's totally unlike us.
对  以后再也别这么做了
Yeah, let's please never do that again.
但是我不能不说我很吃惊
But I can't really say I'm surprised.
你这么一个顶尖的女孩
You are a top-notch lady
是每个男生都梦寐以求的
who any guy would be lucky to have.
现在就为进校队而努力吧
Now let's get us on that varsity squad.
把我的手打成肉酱吧
Turn my hand into a bloody pulp.
暗恋我的人是乔伊·鲁尼
My secret admirer is Joey Rooney.
我的小乔伊终于要和我谈情说爱了啊
My little Joey bird finally chirped back!
等等  乔伊
Wait, Joey?
那封情书和乔伊没有半点瓜葛
There was nothing in that note about Joey...
我这么说是因为那是匿名信嘛
I'm assuming because you said it was a secret.
好几个礼拜以来
For the first time in weeks,
我的思想终于清晰了  我能全神贯注了
my mind is clear and I can concentrate.
我是说  那明显是乔伊写的  对不
I mean, it's obviously Joey, right?
好吧  我知道我应该有权解释清楚
Okay, so I know I should have come clean
来保护我的哥哥
right then and there to protect my brother
和我最好的朋友的  但我的理由是
and my best friend, but in my defense...
好吧  我没啥可说的
Yeah, okay. I got nothing.
当然了  对的
Sure. Yeah.
怎么可能不是呢
Why not?
重点是你终于走出低谷了
The point is that you are out of your slump
现在我们能为选拔赛做准备了
and now we can get you ready for tryouts.
等下  这个嘛
Yeah, about that.
我以后不打垒球了
I'm quitting softball.
什么
What?!
维罗  你不能这么做
Willow, you can't.
情感是要耗工夫的
Relationships take work.
我和乔伊的情感发展
This thing I have going on with Joey
必须成为我的第一要务
has to be my top priority.
等会见了  小玛
See you later, mads,
如果我还能站定的话
if I ever come back down to earth.
哇
Wow.
看来她的乔伊病真的无药可治了
There really is no cure for a bad case of the Joeys.